Let it rain! This is Hana Kojima. And...
Is it this way or that way or is it Talibah or is it Talibah?
Well, shut up.
You're kind of like an ei...
Are you making fun of me?
He's making fun of me.
It's so perfect. Your voice is so perfect.
I really thought so.
You really should sing at your birthday party.
Hana-chan can do songs you can't sing without expressiveness.
Godiva, right?
I thought she looked so graceful while eating her greeting.
But after that, you'll come out?
Yes. I come out afterwards as an intention.
Michiko Furumon.
I wondered what this really meant,
It seems like everyone's name is Narita Kana or something, almost like it's your name.
It's true that they do kind of mangle their first names and so on.
Rumpan and Ruri are both called Runa-Ruri,
Rinati also has "Rina" in her name,
Furumon Michiko, which is almost exactly like the name.
Or even Hanako Furumon,
It's almost like it's not me.
No, it's not. Like this. Like this.
Like that.Yes, but.
Yes, but...
You're in it.
But you're Furumon Michiko from Michiko, right?
That's right.
I thought "Hanako Furumon" wasn't good enough,
What do you mean "Michiko Furumon" at all? I was like, "What do you mean, it's not Furumon Hanako at all?
I wanted to be Michiko, after all.
I couldn't give up on Michiko.
I thought it was better not to fail 70% of the time.
How did you like it? After playing Michiko.
After playing Michiko.
Well, really, it was a bit of a play on the Doctor X character,
She injects Renatee with an injection.
That's right. Was it a blood draw?
I was going to draw blood,
LINATY is too thin for my arm,
I don't really stick it in and there's no object,
I was wondering if it was safe to stab her,
I was a little worried.
I was swinging it around a lot. I was swinging it a lot.
I was doing it rather well,
Inwardly, you know.
I was worried. I wondered if such a thin arm could handle it.
And he stabbed him twice, right?And you stabbed him twice, right?
Yes, a couple of times. Several times.
What's that? I was saying that.
But I asked her to stab me as a gesture of will.
I never fail with Michiko Furumon.
Seventy percent.
You're too anxious, aren't you?
I absolutely hate it.
I hate playing myself, don't you?
Absolutely.
Don't say it. Don't say it out loud.
Don't fail 70% of the time.
I want you to keep your mouth shut.
If it's 70%, don't say a word.
I don't understand why I'm so confident.
I'm 70% sure I won't fail.
I thought for sure you were wrong.
I didn't listen. I didn't listen.
But after the performance was over,
After that, you know.
It's a cute zone.
Secret bass is so cute.
It was so emo.
He's good and emo.He's good and emo.
And cute.
I wanted to be in the front row.
I was wondering why I was backstage.
I understand. I was backstage, so I could only see them on the monitor.
Ah, it's so far away. The monitor is so far away.
I can't see my face very well.
The light reflects off the monitors, so you can't see them.
I wanted to be at the front.
At that time.
After that, I loved it.
He's so cute.
It's over, isn't it? I'm glad it's over.
It's over, isn't it? I'm glad.
I thought you'd hate it.
Our waiting area backstage was right behind the stage,
So if we shouted or something,
I could hear it really loudly.
I could hear Haruyama's voice.
No kidding?
I held back during the performance,
But during rehearsal, I could hear him so well that it was really fun.
Seriously? I'm sorry.
I can hear you.
I don't remember what I said.I don't remember what I said.
I don't.
It's that close.
So I was told to be quiet right away.
I thought I was going to get very angry.
Right?
I heard that.
So I know I shouldn't yell too much,
I love, love, love it.
You were cute and cool.
It was cute and cool.
They fit together perfectly. That's what twins do.
That's right. But they don't have much in common.
Not at all.
We didn't have time to meet Uka-chan either,
Still, I think it's amazing that the two of them have such a good vibe together.
She was so cute.
This cute zone was amazing.
Waka-chan's Cherry Boon was amazing.
Because earlier,
You were looking so good,
Suddenly..,
What?
She's so cute.
We weren't even doing the show,I didn't do the show,
I didn't do the show, but during rehearsal, after Cherry Cherry Boom,
I remember you called me "Senkyu" after Cherry Cherry Boom.
It was so cute.
You know what? You know what I mean?
She was so girly,
I was like, "Thank you.
I was like, "Thank you," too.
Boy.
Cherry Boone.
He was so cute.
She's so cute, she's a little bit of a gap between the two of us.
He's such a good looking guy.
He was doing something like changing his voice depending on the song.
That kind of thing,
When it's a song with a cute sound,
He has such a cute voice,
I think he's like, "Oh, Mr. Talk..." when he plays spring songs.
I'm like, "Hey!
I have a different voice for that kind of thing.
What? Have you ever used two different voices?
That's a lie, not at all.
I don't sing cute songs.
I see. Sorry, sorry.
He does.Because he has.
I really wish he would stop! This.
I don't know what song this is.
I don't either.
Isn't it for a play or something? Stage productions.
I don't sing in stage productions either,
Basically, I don't sing, and I don't have a role,
I don't sing in stage productions either. I don't sing in stage productions either,
I see.
I've never done that much work with different voices,
I admire you.
It's hard to understand.
It was a time of respect.
It was amazing.
It's not easy to be like that,
You don't see that unless you're with other groups of friends.
You don't see that. You don't see that.
You don't work together, and you don't get to ask them, "How are you doing? You don't get to ask them.
You have to get together with them at live performances.
So I thought it was a good opportunity.
Tokyo Akan Land.
It was good, wasn't it?
So, that was it. In the end, 5 years later, I was in a car accident.
I was in a car accident.I was in a car accident.
I saved him, didn't I?
I did.
I saved her and she got into a traffic accident.
Kana-chan.
Only her name was in the script,
Oh, I didn't appear in the script.
But she survived.
Everyone survived.
She said she saved them.
I saved them without failure.
Once the success rate dropped to 60%. The success rate dropped to 60%.
The success rate went down to 60%,
Because you healed me,
I raised it to 70%.
Good, we raised it to 70%.
Mr. Kozue, I was the cause of the problem.
Stop being the cause.
At the end, right?
Don't lose. We all sang together, didn't we?
That was good.
It was like a good aura.
Mi-chan was so cute.
She was cute.
She seemed like the main character.It's like the main character, isn't it?
I'm like, "I'm doing my best,
You're doing a great job.
What was that?
"May God bless you all.
I don't know. I'm pretty sure it's not that.
You shouldn't talk. I really shouldn't.
You'll think I'm making fun of you.
I'm not. I didn't.
I'm not.
I should tell Miichan.
I'm not doing it. Thanks for the gummies. They were delicious.
I won't be forgiven.
I can't do it. I'm scared.
But, what a lot of people are saying.
I was thinking, "Don't lose,
I wondered what I was going to do,
I thought, "I'm going to give a message to my fans.
If it were me, I would definitely run and try to somehow keep the mood alive.
You can't lose, can you?
What? What would you do, Haga? What would you do during that time?
I'd do what I would do,
This is the one.
But if it were me,
I'd take it. I would take it.That's right. I knew you'd take it.
I'm poking and clapping.
That's right.
After all, now they are running, right?
If it were me, I would imitate the 24-hour TV show,
Run like this,
I'm almost there! and have them say something like, "You're almost there!
It's so tedious. I wish they wouldn't put in that kind of acting.
I'm feeling so good.
That's probably the only way to get through it.
That's true.
So..,
I'm trying to send a message to everyone.
I can do it. I thought it was amazing.
I thought she was an idol.
No, it was amazing.
Like, "Don't let them beat you.
And the dance moves, too.
I put that in on the day. Actually.
Backstory. Actually.
Backstory.
We thought it would be better if we all danced together, so we choreographed it.
I was so anxious when I arrived on the day of the event.
And I was in the front of the line, wasn't I?
I was in the front.It was the lead.
That's right. That's why I said I was worried about being in the lead,
I had always thought I was fast,
I wondered what he was worried about,
I was really anxious. Because, remember? That time.
Surprisingly, I was able to do it.
It's amazing that you were able to do it. I was doing something like that without knowing what it was.
You are good at doing something like that, aren't you?
I'm good at it. I can fake it with my face.
Even if I'm wrong, I put on a face that says, "I'm fine.
It's like I'm doing it right. I'm good at it.
Then everyone around me will think I'm wrong.
So, even though I'm sure I'm right,
I start to feel like maybe I'm wrong.
Of course you do.
But Ira is better than me.
Ira is better?
Ira is amazing. Really.
I thought I was wrong, and I really thought Ira was right.
He's really a pro.
He seems really good.
He's really good.
So I learned from him and worked hard.
I see.
I have a mirror named Ira, so even if I make a mistake, it's okay.There's a mirror named Ira, so even if you make a mistake, it's okay, Pai-Sen.
There's a smug-looking man there.
That's huge.
You should learn Ira.
I'll learn.
Even if you make a mistake, you won't be caught.
I'll learn. If I make a mistake, they'll know.
Right in my face.
Like, "I did it! I'll show it right away.
Oh my God, seriously.
Even when I'm ready to vomit, I'm like, "I did it," and I immediately let it out downstairs.
Don't let me do it.
I go down right away.
I'm old-fashioned in my reactions.
You're not going to throw up?
No, I won't. I'm not going to do it.
You're not going to say, "I did it!"?
I won't do it.
The bottom comes out on its own.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'll go down like Teko.
I don't think it's better to keep it out.
But it comes out.
But that's the way it is.
The last one is the standard Ambiance Japan.The last one is still the standard Ambiance Japan.
That's right.
Before that, I have my own corner.
It's the standard Ambiance Japan.
It's over.
Aya2ya, you know.
I hope I've solved your problems.
Wait a minute.
That's great. That was a great ending.
And after that, we saw them off and went home.
Wait a minute. Don't let it end.
That was great.
Are you winding up? Today.
Volume 2.
Are you curling today?
It's not too late.
I think there's volume 3.
Hey.
You're a nightingale, aren't you?
But it's going to come out, right?
I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
Can we go on?
So it's almost the end of the day.
You're forcing me to go on, aren't you?
What was it?What was it again?
That. The voice of the solution to your problems.
I'm going to solve Kana Narita's problems.
No, it's not. Is it "Solving your problems"?
I don't remember.
We did a corner on "Can you solve my problems?
But then, so did the fans.
I think we were able to solve their problems.
It went better than I thought it would.
You didn't think so?
I didn't think so.
Hey.
Why? I was pretty nervous in the beginning. I was.
I was in a hurry.
I was in a big hurry, and I was told I was going to be the MC.
I was asked to be the MC?
I thought it was unusual for Kaliba to be the MC.
It's unusual, and you are not the type of person who turns things around.
I'm more the type of person who is turned.
I'm the type that gets passed around, and I'm the type that interrupts the passing around.
Is that unusual?
I was a little nervous because it was unusual, but it went better than I expected.
Yes, it did. I'm glad that the fans got a good feeling from the show,
We'll be back tomorrow with another interview between the two of you.
You try to end things quickly, don't you?You're trying to get it over with.
Do you want to go home?
I don't want to go home.
I won't let you.
That's the worst.
But really, I was saved by the funny MC of Kaliba.
Oh, no. Thank you for the food.
It was fun.
Really? Thank you very much.
What's with the handshake? I definitely don't need it.
And just like that, we were done with the Ambitious Japan event,
I was so happy to see Morning Musume。 It was a fun time.
Yay!
How was it? Once again.
Look back on it.
There aren't many times to look back like this.
Live performances one by one.
So I was glad to be able to look back with those who were at the show.
There are times when you can't remember what you were doing.
Yes, there are times when I can't remember.
That's why I'm glad.
I'm glad. I'm sure it was.
And I'm glad I'm Harima.
I'm glad, too.
What's up with that? From this group.Something. From this fellow.
Yes. You can say anything.
I guess I get a little nervous.
With that kind of person, you know. I get nervous.
You have to do it right.
Yes, that's right. I feel like I have to answer seriously.
I would have preferred Harima or Rumpan.
Yes, yes. I'm glad we hit it.
It was good. It was a blind date.
It was fun.
Volume 3 is also likely to be available.
I'm sure there will be.
Please come and look forward to it.
So tomorrow, we will be back with another dialogue between the two of us.
Please look forward to it as well.
So, up to this point, I have been talking with Kojimahana of Ameflasi and
and Harimakana.
See you tomorrow!